Where is my brother?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
I know what I've seen. I'm not crazy!
What did you do to my brother?
Where is my brother?
He was on the Prometheus.
He found out
what you were doing on these ships.
I'm not crazy!
Wake up.
You fell asleep.
Where's the boy?
They locked him in.
They did what?
Are you insane?
You can't just lock him in there.
Don't. Please.
Did you give the order to do that?
They threw him off the goddamn railing.
No way someone survives that.
And yet. here he is.
How's that possible?
Let him out!
First. you tell me why your name is
on the passenger list of the Prometheus.
Who are you really?
♪ One pill makes you larger ♪
♪ And one pill makes you small ♪
♪ And the ones that Mother gives you ♪
♪ Don't do anything at all ♪
♪ When logic and proportion ♪
♪ Have fallen sloppy dead ♪
♪ And the White Knight is
Talking backwards ♪
♪ And the Red Queen's off with her head ♪
We're still in control.
Even if they take the bridge.
We could block the steering.
As long as we hold the machine room.
we're in charge.
And I say we hold our course to America.
How far from land are we?
Four days. maybe three.
What will they do with us when we arrive?
Mutiny carries the death penalty.
Justice is always
on the side of the survivors.
The Light will always prevail.
We're not going to surrender.
Even if it means more sacrifices.
Remember the time
when Ada bathed the piglet in the font?
She was always different
from the rest of us.
And she was never afraid of Mother.
You know it's not true. right?
You know she's sick.
Mother.
The voices she hears.
that's not the voice of God.
She created her own world.
Her own truths. We all just followed her.
But hearing voices is not a sign of God.
It's a sign of madness.
What if she's right?
Do you honestly think
all this is the will of God?
After all that has happened.
You helped her kill that boy.
It's not like you haven't killed before.
That was different.
You promised me
we would leave them. together.
You promised me we would leave them
as soon as we came to America. With Ada.
What are you doing?
Something I should have done
a long time ago.
Tove.
Were you ever
in love with me? Even for one day?
It's so easy for you.
You have all you could ever need.
You don't realize how hard others have
to struggle to get to where you are.
So it was all a lie.
You're not a lieutenant.
Your father never owned any land.
That uncle of yours
in Marseille doesn't even exist.
You want to know
if I was ever really in love with you?
Every morning. I wake up wishing I wasn't.
You are a constant reminder
of what I can't have.
A life.
Love.
You.
Captain?
What do we do now?
Hey! Don't shoot.
Please don't shoot. I'm here to help.
Okay?
I'll help stop my mother.
What was that? What's in there?
Huh?
Stay away from the cabinet!
- I said stay away!
- No! Don't!
That was you. wasn't it?
Did that thing do this?
Who are you?
You tell me what's going on.
Now!
Talk to me!
Olek.
What?
Fuck.
What's that noise?
Stop.
Where are you taking me?
What's happening?
Hey. please!
What is this?
My God. what now?
This is it. We're all going to die.
Last night.
you and Miss Franklin.
what did you talk about?
I don't see
what that's got to do with anything.
Do you know her?
- I was just offering my help.
- Where is she?
- I don't know!
Hey! Stop it.
Stop!
You are the captain.
What do you want to do?
I don't know
what's going on here.
I have no idea
how any of this is possible.
But what I do know is that
all of this is not our only problem.
They've been firing the furnaces
full speed since yesterday.
If they keep going like that.
we'll run out of coal
in the next two days.
We'll be lost in the ocean.
We need to ration the coal
until we find land.
He's right.
We need to take the ship
back under control.
It stopped. And now?
What is going on?
It sounds like a clock.
What is happening?
What are you doing?
Mom?
What's going on?
You are crew. You have to know
what that sound means.
What?
What are you looking at me for?
I don't know what it is.
Krester?
Krester!
Landon.
Landon. are you all right?
Oi.
Where do you think you going?
Landon!
Where are they going?
God help us.
The Devil is calling them.
Eugen!
Stop. Halt. Stop!
Mom!
What are you doing?
No.
Stop!
No!
I think that was a body!
What's going on?
Where are they going?
What is happening?
What is happening out there?
What is that ticking sound?
Talk to me.
I can't tell you.
You'll have to ask the Creator.
- Lower your guns!
- First lower yours!
They're jumping overboard.
What are you talking about?
Where is Krester?
Dad. Where is Krester?
He jumped.
No.
I couldn't save him.
They're all jumping overboard!
All of them!
They're all killing themselves!
Don't let them through!
- Where are you going?
- Stop them!
Stop!
Please!
Come on.
Stop right there!
Hello!
Hello! Can you hear me?
We'll have to tie them up.
Everyone stop!
Stop right there!
Where are you going?
Stop!
Are you okay?
She jumped...
Stop! Stop!
Don't be afraid.
Fuck!
You shouldn't have done that.
It knows we're here now.
We've never made it this far.
Maybe it will work this time.
You brought her here?
She didn't remember.
We don't have much time.
I need to stop this
before they sink the ship.
I need you to stay here
for a while. all right?
He won't find you.
I promise.
Ángel!
Ángel. it's me. open the door!
♪ The tarara has ♪
- ♪ A wounded little finger that... ♪
- Ángel.
- ♪No surgeon can cure ♪
Stop!
What are you waiting for?
You'd actually be doing me a favor.
Sit down.
Tie him up!
Your turn.
What the fuck are you doing?
Kill me! Just get it over with!
Why are you doing this?
I didn't come here to kill you.
I'm trying to save your life.
Whatever's happening out there.
I am sure it's contagious.
Quickly. tie them up.
He jumped.
He just jumped.
Mother. listen to me.
- Mother. it will be all right. Mother!
- And ourselves.
- Mother!
- Hey!
Tove!
Why doesn't he stop it?
I shouldn't have let my mom come with me.
It is all my fault.
You will live.
I promise.
Come on. Come on.
Hey. you. What are you doing there?
I was just...
The captain sent me
to have a look at this.
I'm one of the engineers
from the ship company.
Where did everyone go?
Everyone just left. Did I miss an order?
What does that thing even do anyway?
Who did you say you were again?
It doesn't matter.
What's that?
Fuck.
Oi. what is that?
Look!
- I think you should leave.
- Why?
I don't want to hurt you. Just leave.
Hurt me?
What is that?
Fuck.
Landon was right.
You're one of them!
You're a wolf!
You stay away from me!
You don't understand.
If I don't turn that thing off.
everything will start again.
What... What are you talking about?
Fuck!
Don't!
Stop!
Where is it?
Father.
Where did you hide it?
This is not real. You are not real.
How did I get here?
How is this possible?
Where is Ciaran?
What have you done with him?
Where is my brother?
You're not asking the right questions.
He found out. didn't he?
What you're doing here.
On these ships.
No. don't!
No!
Please stop. Please don't do this.
Please don't do this.
Wake up.
Eyk.
How did you do that?
How did you just disappear?
It's the boy!
That thing he had. the pyramid...
I know that this sounds crazy.
but he somehow stopped time with it.
You're right.
I didn't tell you everything.
Maura Franklin.
that's not the name I was born with.
Franklin is my mother's maiden name.
I was born Maura Singleton.
As in the company that bought the ships?
Henry Singleton. he's my father.
I think that this is
some kind of experiment.
My father devoted his life
to the study of human behavior.
He is obsessed with understanding
the brain and all its functions.
He was never interested in owning ships.
I'm sure he did something to these ships
to study the passengers on board.
That envelope that you showed me?
I received the same.
I think it's from my brother.
Henry.
It's addressed to your father?
It's short for Henriette.
My middle name.
That's what my brother used to call me.
When we were children.
we didn't get along.
My father didn't try to hide
that he preferred me over my brother.
That's why he chose that name for me.
He thought I was slowly turning into
a version of our father.
You think your brother sent this?
About four months ago. he contacted me.
He wanted to meet
at the docks in Southampton.
He was secretive. He said he'd
found out something about our father.
I went and waited. but he never showed up.
Then I learned that.
one day earlier. the Prometheus.
one of ships my father had bought.
had left that same dock.
He's been missing for four months.
The amount of time
the Prometheus has been missing
and the same amount of time
that I lost my...
Don't move.
Help me with this?
Okay.
I don't know how it works.
but somehow. this thing opens doors.
This is impossible.
♪ Thoughts are free ♪
♪ Who can guess what they might be? ♪
Do you hear that?
♪ They fly by ♪
♪ Like shadows in the night ♪
♪ No one can know them ♪
♪ No hunter can shoot them ♪
♪ And so it'll always be
Thoughts are free ♪
Whose house is that?
It's mine.
How is this possible?
We're on a ship.
How does a whole landscape
fit inside a ship?
This isn't the only one.
There's another shaft.
It's beneath my bed.
Thank God. you're back.
They're all killing themselves.
I tried to contact the ship company.
And this is what they replied.
The captain was right.
We must change course. return to Europe.
What is that?
Nothing you need
concern yourself with now.
You think your father did all that?
And the people out there dying.
he somehow caused that too?
I'm not sure they actually are dying.
How can any of this be real?
You think this is some kind of dream?
Whatever it is.
I think I found out before.
but he somehow made me forget again.
He made you forget?
I remember being a doctor
at a mental hospital.
but he somehow tries to make me
believe I was a patient instead.
I don't remember who I am.
The passenger list
you found on the Prometheus...
I don't remember being on that ship.
but what if I was?
That list...
Your name on it...
It's not the only strange thing on there.
This is my signature.
I don't know how any of this is possible.
But I think I was
the captain of the Prometheus.
It stopped.
The sound. It stopped.
You came back.
Of course I came back.
Mother.
Krester. Krester.
Krester.
It'll be all right. Mother.
It will be all right.
What's going on?
- I think we're safe now.
- Safe from what?
Jérôme.
What's going on?
Miss Franklin.
It's... so good to see you.
I just had...
one of the strangest dreams.
Is that everyone?
Are we the only ones left?
Captain.
I think you should see this.
They keep sending the same thing.
"Sink ship."
Why would they send
the same message again?
I don't think they mean the Prometheus.
I think they mean us.
Sir. we just received an alert
from Project Kerberos.
Tell him
he doesn't have much more time.
He needs to bring me the boy.
♪ Misty morning ♪
♪ Clouds in the sky ♪
♪ Without warning. a wizard walks by ♪
♪ Casting his shadow. weaving his spell ♪
♪ Funny clothes. tinkling bell ♪
♪ Evil power disappears ♪
♪ Demons worry when the wizard is near ♪
♪ He turns tears into joy ♪
♪ Everyone's happy
When the wizard walks by ♪
♪ Never talking ♪
♪ Just keeps walking ♪
♪ Spreading his magic ♪
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-